A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, SG 1.24 (A98) FA1295
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Agricultural Sciences (AS), 1990-1997
  - 94-8100-26 - Universidad Autonoma Chapingo - Training Course on Agroforestry for Ecodevelopment, 1993-1997 (Box R3150)
- Equal Opportunity (EO), 1988-1997
  - EO 8850 - Persistent Poverty - National Forum, 1988-1997 (Box R3150)
  - EO 9012 - Brandeis University - Archive and Evaluation Projects, 1988-1995; 3 files. (Box R3150)
  - EO 9044 - Hunter College - Latino Study, 1990-1993; 1996; 3 files. (Box R3151)
  - EO 9225 - Sherraden, Michael - Publish Book on Central Provident Fund of Singapore, 1992-1996 (Box R3151)
  - EO 9227 - University of Texas, Austin - Agenda '92: The Children of San Antonio, 1992-1995 (Box R3151)
  - EO 9230 - Twentieth Century Fund - Race Relations in the Military: Implications for Civilian Society, 1992-1995 (Box R3151)
  - EO 9242 - Californina Community Foundation - Multi-Cultural Collaborative: Organized as a Response to Los Angeles Riots, 1992-1995 (Box R3151)
  - EO 9301 - National Puerto Rican Coalition - Advocacy and Policy Analysis Strategy, 1992-1996 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9302 - Philanthropic Initiative - Contaminated Sites in the United States, 1993-1994 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9303 - Council for Community-Based Development - General Operations, 1988-1993; 1996 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9304 - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund - South Central Los Angeles Leadership Development Program and Rebuild Los Angeles, 1991-1996 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9305 - Manpower Demonstration Research Corp. - Lessons on Unpaid Work Experience, 1993-1994 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9309 - Johns Hopkins University - Effects of Housing Assistance on Recipients, 1993-1995 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9311 - Morehouse College - National Conference Honoring Anniversary of Publication, 1993-1994 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9312 - Manpower Demonstration Research Corp. (MDRC) - Community-Economic Development and Employment Training, 1993-1994 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9316 - Public-Private Ventures - Career Ladders and Secondary Market Jobs for Low-Skilled Youth, 1992-1996; 2 files. (Box R3152)
  - EO 9317 - Tides Foundation - Grantmakers' Income Security Task Force, 1992-1995 (Box R3152)
  - EO 9318 - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities - Multi-Phase Communications Plan, 1993-1995 (Box R3153)
  - EO 9319 - Urban Institute - Conference on Self-Sufficiency for the Low-Skilled in Today's Labor Market, 1993-1994 (Box R3153)
  - EO 9325 - Housing Partnership Development Corp. - New Employment Opportunities for the Homeless, 1993 (Box R3153)
  - EO 9327 - Manpower Demostration Research Corporation - Welfare Recipients Who Exceed Two-Year Limit, 1993-1995 (Box R3153)
  - 94-8020-6 - National Congress for Community Economic Development - Conference on Human Capital in the Community Development Field, 1994-1997 (Box R3153)
- Health Sciences (HS), 1986-1998
  - HS 8923 - University of Virginia - Cryptosporidiosis, 1989-1992; 1997 (Box R3153)
  - HS 9101 - Harvard University - "Good Health in Africa" Conference, 1990-1996 (Box R3153)
  - HS 9135 - Carvajal Foundation - Environmental Recycling Program, 1990-1996 (Box R3153)
  - HS 9142 - University of Mississippi - Dengue Fever, 1990-1994 (Box R3153)
  - HS 9204 - Trustees of Health and Hospitals of the City of Boston, Inc. - "Healthy Boston" Initiative, 1991-1993; 1996-1998 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9227 - Mahidol University - Support Participants at XIIIth International Congress for Tropical Medicine and Malaria, 1992-1993; 1997 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9228 - Harvard University - New Public Health Programs, 1989-1997 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9230 - Task Force for Child Survival and Development - Evaluate Performance of Tetanus Toxoid Vaccine, 1992-1995 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9248 - University of Dublin (Trinity College) - Dengue Viral Research, 1992-1995 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9250 - Pan American Health Organization - Review of International Health Agencies, 1992-1996 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9252 - National Academy of Science - Institute of Medicine - International Health, 1987-1993; 1996-1998 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9301 - Thomas Jefferson University - Rabies Treatment, 1992-1994 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9303 - University of California, Davis - Risk Factors for Sexually Transmitted Diseases Among Sub-Saharan African Women, 1991-1995 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9304 - Harvard University - Health Implications in Developing Countries, 1992-1994 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9305 - American College of Clinical - Second International Advanced Clinical Engineering Workshop, 1992-1993 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9306 - Rockefeller Foundation - Health Sciences Meeting on Data Assessment Needs for Pneumococcal and H. Influenza Vaccine Development, 1993; 1995 (Box R3154)
  - HS 9310 - Task Force for Child Survival - Immunization of Ugandan Children, 1986-1998; 3 files. (Box R3155)
  - HS 9312 - University of North Carolina (Chapel Hill) - Master's in Public Health Program in India, 1992-1997 (Box R3155)
  - HS 9314 - Makerere University (Uganda) - Enable African Women Delegates to Attend Seventh International Women and Health Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box R3155)
  - HS 9315 - Kenya Medical Women's Association - Health of Women and Safe Motherhood Congress, 1993-1996 (Box R3155)
  - HS 9316 - Harvard University - Cost of Workshop on Emerging Diseases, 1993-1994 (Box R3155)
  - HS 9317 - University of Ottawa (Canada) - Conference on International Needs-Based Technology Assessment, 1992-1994 (Box R3155)
  - HS 9318 - World Health Organization (WHO) (Switzerland) - Meeting of Global Network of Collaborating Centre Directors for Arboviruses and Haemorrhagic Fevers, 1993-1994 (Box R3155)
- Population Sciences (PS), 1989-1997
  - PS 9216 - Population Communications International - Impact of Television Series in India, 1991-1994; 2 files. (Box R3158)
  - PS 9233 - Hastings Center - Influence of Long-Term Contraception on Public Policy, 1991-1997; 2 files. (Box R3158)
  - PS 9241 - Overseas Development Council - "Promoting Private Enterprise" Study, 1992-1994 (Box R3158)
  - PS 9243 - World Health Organization - Meeting on Findings of Research on Adolescent Sexual Experience in Africa, 1992-1994 (Box R3158)
  - PS 9247 - Population Council - Effect of Population Growth on the Environment, 1992-1995 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9248 - Peking University - Inner Mongolia Grasslands, 1992-1996 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9301 - National Academy of Sciences - Conference on World Population and Development, 1992-1995 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9302 - Overseas Development Council - Causes and Consequences of Rapid Population Growth, 1992-1996 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9303 - Korea Institute for Health and Social Affairs - Seoul Seminar: Impact of Below Replacement Fertility in East and Southeast Asia, 1992-1994 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9306 - University of Buenos Aires - Oxidative Damage to Sperm, 1989-1996 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9307 - Latin American Social Science Research Council - Conference on Demography Transition, 1992-1993 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9308 - United Nations Economic Commission For Latin America - Publish Report on Women's Migration and Labor Market in Santiago, Chile, 1992-1996 (Box R3159)
  - PS 9309 - Colegio de Mexico - Population Doctoral Program, 1993-1996; 3 files. (Box R3160)
  - PS 9311 - University of Cambridge (England) - BC Conference - Migration Fertility and National Identity, 1992-1994 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9312 - Harvard University - Mobilize Resources for Population and Development Activities, 1992-1995 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9316 - Catholic University (Chile) - Role of Calcium in Oviduct, 1992-1996 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9318 - Climate Institute - Environmental Refugee Program, 1993-1995 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9320 - Peking University - Institute of Population Research - Enable Non-Chinese Students to Attend Postgraduate Program, 1993; 1996 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9325 - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Abortion and Family Planning, 1993-1994 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9329 - Parlimentarians for Global Action - Workshop: Population, Poverty, Consumption and Environment, 1993-1994 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9330 - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population (Belgium) - Seminar on Values and Fertility Change, 1993; 1996 (Box R3160)
  - PS 9335 - World Health Organization (WHO) - Meeting to Prepare a Mother-Baby Package, 1993-1995 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9337 - Badan Koordinasi Kelluarga Berencana Nasional (Indonesia) - Population and Family Planning, 1993-1996 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9338 - Inclen, Inc. - Reproductive Tract Infections in Women Workshop, 1993-1994 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9404 - International Council on Management of Population Programmes (Malaysia) - Family Planning Services in Vietnam, 1992-1995 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9408 - Centro de Pesquisa E Assistencia Em Reproducao Humana (Brazil) - Meeting on Molecular Biology of the Endometrium, 1993-1996 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9410 - Population Sciences - Capacity Building in Sub-Saharan Africa - Program Operations, 1994 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9417 - Reproductive Health Technologies Project, Inc. - Oral Contraceptives in Selected European Countries, 1994 (Box R3161)
  - 94-8120-21 - Kassabian, Lucie - Technical Assistance to the Egyptian NGO Steering Committee, 1994-1995 (Box R3161)
  - 94-8120-24 - World Health Organization (WHO) (Switzerland) - Workshop on Social Science Research on Reproductive Health in South Asia, 1994-1995 (Box R3161)
  - 94-8120-29 - Kabeer, Naila - Fertility Decline in Bangladesh, 1994-1995 (Box R3161)
  - PS 9432 - Rodriguez-Trias, Helen - Public Health Sector Advisor at the United Nations Conference on Population and Development, 1994-1995 (Box R3161)
- Special Interests and Explorations (SIE), 1985-1998
  - SIE 9118 - Harvard University - Journal of Hispanic Policy, 1990-1995 (Box R3161)
  - SIE 9137 - University of Western Cape - Economic Policy Research Project, 1990-1993; 1997 (Box R3161)
  - SIE 9205 - Court Appointed Special Advocates, Inc. - Volunteer Advocacy Project, 1991-1994 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9210 - Women's Dialogue U.S-U.S.S.R - Russian Newsletter on Women's Issues, 1991-1993; 1996 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9213 - Essential Information - Time Dollar Project, 1992-1996 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9217 - Consortium for Global Development - General Support, 1991-1995 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9234 - Brooklyn Historical Society - Bridging Eastern Parkway, 1992-1995 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9305 - Katha - Publication of Tamasha, 1992-1994 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9307 - Physicians for Human Rights - Forensic Investigations of War Crimes in Former Yugoslavia, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9308 - Social Science Research Council - Sexuality Research Assessment Project, 1993-1995 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9309 - American Foundation for AIDS Research - Evaluation of New York City Needle Exchange Program, 1992-1993 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9312 - Philanthropic Initiative - General Support, 1992-1995 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9317 - New York Community Trust - Host Council on Foundations' 1994 Meeting, 1993 (Box R3162)
  - SIE 9319 - Maryland Public Broadcasting Commission - Women's Global Film Project, 1993-1996 (Box R3163)
  - SIE 9320 - United Nations - Fourth World Conference on Women, 1993-1998 (Box R3163)
  - SIE 9323 - National Charities Information Bureau, 1985-1995 (Box R3163)
  - 94-8040-14 - Feminist Majority Foundation - Legal and Relocation Assistance to Women's Health Clinics, 1994-1995 (Box R3163)
  - 94-8040-17 - Chinese Scholars of International Studies, Inc. - Hawaii Conference on China at the Turn of the Century, 1994 (Box R3163)
  - 94-8040-23 - Conference on Non-Governmental Organizations in Consultative Status with the United Nations Economic and Social Council (Congo) - NGO Forum Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box R3163)
- International Security (IS), 1991-1996
  - IP 9301 - Rockefeller Foundation - BC Conference: Strengthening Local Philanthropy, 1992-1994 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9204 - Peace Research Institute Frankfurt - Nuclear Nonproliferation Strategy for Europe, 1991-1995 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9205 - International Peace Academy - General Support, 1991-1994 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9207 - Stimson Center - Chemical Weapons Convention Verification Regime, 1992-1995 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9211 - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - Curtailing of Nuclear Weapons Programs, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9301 - Parlimentarians for Global Action - Multilateral Verification Project, 1992-1993 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9305 - Tahir-Kheli, Shirin - Study Gates Mission to India and Pakistan, 1993-1996 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9308 - Parlimentarians for Global Action - Support in Africa and Asia for Test-Ban-Non-Proliferation, 1993-1994 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9311 - Rockefeller Foundation - International Security Program Operations: Confidence Building and Dialogue in India, 1993; 1997 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9312 - Washington Council on Non-Proliferation - Non-Proliferation Treaty Seminar, 1992-1994 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9317 - Institute for Science and International Security (ISIS) - Training South African Officials, 1993-1994 (Box R3164)
  - IS 9319 - Asia Society - Identify Avenues of Cooperation with North Korea, 1993; 1996 (Box R3165)
  - IS 9320 - Independent University - African and Asian Participation in Moscow Conference on Chemical and Biological Issues, 1993; 1996 (Box R3165)
  - IS 9321 - Carnegie Mellon University - U.S.-India Meeting on Technology Transfer and Weapons of Mass Destruction, 1993-1996 (Box R3165)
  - IS 9323 - Sustainable Development Policy Institute (Pakistan) - Peace and Security Issues in Pakistan, 1993-1996 (Box R3165)
  - IS 9325 - Verification Technology Information Centre (England) - South Asian Transparency and the Military, 1993-1996 (Box R3165)
  - IS 9326 - University of Notre Dame - Middle Eastern and South Asian Participation in Visiting Fellows Program, 1993-1996 (Box R3165)
  - IS 9327 - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities - True Costs of Nuclear Forces, 1993-1996 (Box R3165)
  - 94-8210-3 - Parlimentarians for Global Action - Participation of Jean Krasno at Meetings, 1994 (Box R3165)
  - 94-8210-12 - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War - Fourth Asia-Pacific Regional Conference, 1994-1996 (Box R3165)
  - 94-8210-13 - Parlimentarians for Global Action - Support for Organization for Prohibition of Chemical Weapons, 1994-1996 (Box R3165)
- School Reform (SR), 1990-1996
  - SR 9129 - Michigan State University - District Leadership Academy, 1991-1995 (Box R3165)
  - SR 9302 - ETV Endowment of South Carolina, Inc. - Learning Matters, 1990-1994 (Box R3165)
  - SR 9303 - Greater Kansas City Community Foundation - Early Childhood Immunization Media Campaign, 1993; 1996 (Box R3165)
  - SR 9304 - Editorial Projects in Education - From Risk to Renewal Book, 1993; 1996 (Box R3165)
  - SR 9310 - University of Minnesota - National Survey of College Education Courses, 1993-1995 (Box R3165)
  - SR 9311 - Institute for Educational Leadership, Inc. - Curriculum Reform and Professional Development in District of Columbia Public Schools, 1993-1996 (Box R3165)
  - SR 9312 - National Governors' Association Center for Policy Research - Policy Papers on Children's and Youth's Social and Educational Needs, 1993-1994 (Box R3166)
  - SR 9313 - Harvard University - Publication of a Symposium by the Harvard Educational Review, 1993-1994 (Box R3166)
  - SR 9403 - National Association of Elementary School Principals Foundation - Elementary and Middle School Principals Forum, 1993-1994 (Box R3166)
  - SR 9404 - Council on Foundations - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families, 1992-1996 (Box R3166)
  - 94-8030-8 - American Association for Higher Education - Commission on Chapter 1 Dissemination, 1992-1996 (Box R3166)
  - 94-8030-9 - Wilson, Thomas A. - Book, Reaching for a Better Standard, 1994-1996 (Box R3166)
- United States, 1981-1994; 200
  - Employment Program for Minority Group Female Single Parents - Supplementary Material - ABT Chronological Files, 1982 July-1985 February (Box R3167)
  - Employment Program for Minority Group Female Single Parents - Supplementary Material - ABT Chronological Files, 1985 March-1986 September (Box R3168)
  - Employment Program for Minority Group Female Single Parents - Supplementary Material - Meeting Files, 1985 March-1986 May (Box R3169)
  - Employment Program for Minority Group Female Single Parents - Supplementary Material - Reports and Meeting Files, 1985-1986 (Box R3170)
  - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Photos, 1981-1994 (Box R3176)
- Fellowships, 1987-1998
  - F-PS USA - Barnhart, Kurt Thomas, 1991-1993 (Box R3171)
  - F-AS Mozambique - Bay, Admir Pancas M., 1990-1995 (Box R3171)
  - F-PS England - Brown, Jeremy J. G., 1991-1994 (Box R3171)
  - F-AS China - Cao, Yongwei, 1988-1994 (Box R3171)
  - F-PS India - Chaudhary, Jaideep, 1991-1995 (Box R3171)
  - F-AS Korea - Choi Seong Ho, 1989-1993 (Box R3171)
  - F-PS Pakistan - Chugtai, Saleem Z., 1992-1993 (Box R3171)
  - F-PS USA - Curran, Sara Reynolds, 1991-1993 (Box R3171)
  - F-AS MALI - Dembele, Niama Nango, 1989-1994 (Box R3171)
  - F-PS Nigeria - Ezeh, Alex Chika, 1991-1995 (Box R3171)
  - F-AS China - Fan Zaifeng, 1989-1996 (Box R3171)
  - F-AS China - Gan Susheng, 1988-1997 (Box R3172)
  - F-PS USA - Gillet, Rhonda M., 1992-1995 (Box R3172)
  - F-AS India - Grover, Anil, 1992-1996 (Box R3172)
  - F-AS Bangladesh - Hossain, M. Anwar, 1989-1996 (Box R3172)
  - F-PS India - Jaiswal, Yogesh K., 1988-1994 (Box R3172)
  - F-PS Nepal - Joshi, Arun Raj, 1991-1993 (Box R3172)
  - F-AS India - Khehra, Gurpreet S., 1989-1995 (Box R3172)
  - F-AS Zimbabwe - Khombe, C. T., 1989-1994 (Box R3172)
  - F-AS India - Kishor, P. B. Kavi, 1990-1995 (Box R3172)
  - F-PS Byelorussia - Krupenko, N. I., 1990-1995 (Box R3172)
  - F-AS Korea - Lee, Jang-Yong, 1988-1994 (Box R3172)
  - F-PS China - Li Xue-Jun, 1991-1994 (Box R3172)
  - F-PS China - Liang Zai, 1991-1994 (Box R3173)
  - F-AS China - Liu Dong, 1989-1995 (Box R3173)
  - F-PS Uganda - Lubega, Margaret, 1990-1995 (Box R3173)
  - F-AS Zimbabwe - Mano, Reneth, 1988-1997 (Box R3173)
  - F-PS India - Nath, Dlip Chandra, 1990-1994 (Box R3173)
  - F-AS Cameroon - Ngon A. Yassi, Martin, 1989-1994 (Box R3173)
  - F-PS Nigeria - Olaleye, Oyewole, 1991-1994 (Box R3173)
  - F-AS Sri Lanka - Perera, Athula Lokha-Maniya Thilak, 1991-1997 (Box R3173)
  - F-AS Egypt - Ragab, Ragab Abdel-Khalik, 1991-1994 (Box R3173)
  - F-PS India - Rao, Jaladanki N., 1991-1996 (Box R3173)
  - F-PS India - Reddi, Poothi P., 1990-1995 (Box R3174)
  - F-PS India - Reddy, Ramalingam L., 1990-1994 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS Zimbabwe - Rusike, Joseph, 1988-1995 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS Philippines - Saliba-Tarun, Alice Sacluti, 1989-1995 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS Philippines - Sebastian, Leocadio, 1990-1994; 1998 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS India - Shashidhar, Halagappa E., 1992-1996 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS India - Sheoran, Inder Singh, 1990-1995 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS India - Singh, Sukhwinder, 1991-1994; 1998 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS India - Sivamani, Elumalai, 1991-1995 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS Indonesia - Slamet, Inez Hortense, 1991-1994 (Box R3174)
  - F-AS India - Subramanian, Vaidyanathan, 1991-1996 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS Indonesia - Sutrisno, Dr., 1991-1994 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS Nigeria - Tonukari, Nyerhovwo John, 1993-1995 (Box R3175)
  - F-PS Mexico - Villalpando Fierro, Maria Irma, 1989-1992 (Box R3175)
  - F-HS Uganda - Wabwire-Mangen, Fred, 1987-1994 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS China - Wang Mingbo, 1989-1995 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS China - Wang Zhimin, 1992-1998 (Box R3175)
  - F-PS China - Xin Tan, 1991-1995 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS China - Xu Baoji, 1988-1994 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS China - Xu De-Ping, 1988-1996 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS India - Yadav, Neelam R., 1991-1995 (Box R3175)
  - F-PS China - Yang Liang-Sheng, 1990-1996 (Box R3175)
  - F-PS China - Yang, Quanhe, 1990-1995 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS China - Zhang Guangming, 1992-1995 (Box R3175)
  - F-AS China - Zhou Zong-Ming, 1988-1995 (Box R3175)
- Program and Policy - General, 1949-1987; 900
  - Fellowships - Postdoctoral Fellowship Program in Social Sciences and Rural Development, 1982-1986 (Box R3177)
  - Fellowships - Postdoctoral Fellowship Program in Social Sciences and Rural Development - Evaluation, 1982-1984; 4 files. (Box R3177)
  - Financial Administration - Finance Committee Reports - 1-10, 1982-1984 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Friedlander), 1970-1980 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Katz), 1985 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Monet), 1981 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Parker), 1974-1983 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Spelman Prentice Trust), 1987 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Studley, J. J.), 1986 (Box R3178)
  - Financial Administration - Gifts (Wills), 1980-1982 (Box R3178)
  - New York City Corporate Citizens Committee, 1984-1985 (Box R3178)
  - Officers - Vice Presidential Search, 1980-1983 (Box R3178)
    Restricted - Open in 2024.
  - Organization - Reports (ORG 37-41), 1949-1951; 1978-1979 (Box R3178)
  - Program and Policy, 1974-1977 (Box R3179)
  - Program and Policy - China, 1972-1979; 3 files. (Box R3179)
    Includes report.
  - Program and Policy - Evaluation, 1971-1982; 3 files. (Box R3180)
  - Program and Policy - Evaluation - Supplementary Material - Statistical Data, 1972-1983 (Box R3180)
  - Program and Policy - Evaluation - Supplementary Material - Reports, 1976; 1982 (Box R3180)
  - Program and Policy - Grants-In-Aid, 1972 (Box R3181)
  - Program and Policy - Health Program History, 1979-1984 (Box R3181)
  - Program and Policy - Plant Resistance and Protection - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R3181)
  - Program and Policy - Plant Resistance and Protection, 1971-1980; 4 files. (Box R3181)
  - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Associate Director Search, 1982-1983 (Box R3182)
  - Program and Policy - Population and Health - Health Sciences Review, 1982-1983; 2 files. (Box R3182)
  - Program and Policy - Women, 1981-1986; 5 files total. (Box R3182)
  - Program and Policy - Women, 1981-1986; 5 files total. (Box R3183)
  - Program and Policy - Women - Supplementary Material - Background, 1981-1984 (Box R3183)
  - Program and Policy - Women - Supplementary Material - Seven Springs Conference, 1982 (Box R3183)
- Program and Policy - Members and Meetings, 1970-1984; 903
  - Members and Meetings - Bellagio Meetings, 1984; 1989 (Box R3183)
  - Members and Meetings - Atlanta Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box R3183)
  - Members and Meetings - Mexico Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box R3183)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - American Electric Power, 1975 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - American Home Products, 1977. 1979 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - American Metal Climax, 1974 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Beatrice Foods Company, 1978 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Bethlehem Steel, 1974 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Bristol-Meyers, 1975-1976; 1979 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Citicorp, 1977-1979 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Dresser Industries, Inc., 1980 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Eastman Kodak, 1974 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Exxon, 1976 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Firestone, 1975 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Ford Motor, 1972 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - General Electric, 1973-1974; 1977 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - General Motors, 1970-1973 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Georgia-Pacific, 1978 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Gulf and Western Industries, 1980 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - IBM, 1973-1974 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Kaufman and Broad, 1975 (Box R3184)
  - Members and Meetings - Proxies - Merick, 1976 (Box R3184)